

#### PERSONAL INFO

**Location**Bangalore

Phone number +918086141144

Email id chandana.04nair@gmail.com

#### **INTERESTS**

- Reading
- Dancing
- Traveling
- Spending time with my pets

### LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi
- Malayalam
- Tamil
- Arabic

# CHANDANA NAIR

Sales & Marketing professional with 10 years of experience driving profitability through strategic growth & leading teams. Fiercely competitive in my approach to acquire business and able to handle complex situations from a strategic perspective.

#### **EDUCATION**

**MBA – International Business** 

Jul 2018

ICFAI University, Sikkim

BTech – Electronics & Communication

Jul 2013

MG University, Kerala

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Senior Account Manager

Jan 2022 - Present

Promolta IT Solutions Pvt Ltd, Bangalore.

- Carry out direct communication and negotiation with top tier clients.
- Upselling and cross-selling company services.
- Building high quality partnerships with clients and helping retention.
- Strategizing in acquiring old clients.
- Training and mentoring team members to up-skills.
- Developing and implementing a timeline to achieve targets and delegating tasks to team members.
- Oversee day-to-day team's operation and conducting quarterly performance reviews.

# Relationship Manager

Mar 2021 - Sept 2021

IndusInd Bank, Bangalore.

- Build long term relationship with clients and customers.
- Research and pursue new business opportunities.
- Ensure new sales and cross-selling.
- Want to address and resolve existing customer issues.
- Ensure client satisfaction.

Account Manager- Client Servicing & Marketing Jun 2017 – Aug 2020 Excito Events, Trivandrum.

- Build relationships with client based on trust and respect.
- Identifying industry trends.
- Keeping accurate records pertaining to inventory and account notes.
- Deal with client requests and troubleshoot problems.
- Participate in market campaigns.
- Inspire repeat business from clients.
- Generating new business leads.

# **Accounts and Marketing Administrator**

Sept 2014 - Mar 2017

Khimji International LLC, Sultanate of Oman.

- Manage administration of Accounts and Marketing section.
- Execute online promotional strategy through various social network.
- Expand dealer market and have regular meetings to ensure smooth flow of business.
- Execute measures for promoting and carrying out marketing activities.
- Maintain customers and assist in generating marketing reports.

# **Business Development Associate**

Jul 2013 - Aug 2014

Yarab Technologies Pvt Ltd, Trivandrum

- Identify and help to develop strategic relationships with partners or potential customers in UK.
- Assists in the development of a strong pipeline of new customers and projects in accounts through direct or indirect customer contact and prospecting.
- Increasing the value of current customers while attracting new ones.

I hereby bring into your notice that above mentioned information is true to the best of my knowledge. I bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above-mentioned particulars.

Place: Bengaluru CHANDANA NAIR